[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay, this is exciting.
好的，多么令人兴奋
We reminded ourselves of gradient descent and what that looks like.
让我们回忆一下梯度下降，它讲了些什么
We figured out what the discretion model is.
离散模型是
We talked about maximum likelihood functions and estimation.
最大化似然函数和估计值
And we can solve quite a bit of the math.
我们可以解决一些数学问题
Now, lets dive in and look at the actual learning algorithm for
现在，让我们深入学习并看一看
logistic regression.
逻辑回归的实际学习算法
That learning algorithm's going to be extremely simple.
这个学习算法相当的简单
And so, in spite of the math we've seen, we are going to come up algorithm that you
因此，尽管我们已经了解了一些数学表达式，现在我们将
can implement in just a couple lines of code.
通过编写几行代码来实现该算法
To, this final graded ascent algorithm for logistic regression,
逻辑回归的最终梯度下降算法
all we have to do is fine the derivative, with respect to each parameter, wj.
我们需要做的就是对每一个参数wj求偏导
So what's the derivative for likelihood function with respect to wj?
那似然函数对参数wj求偏导是什么样的
By the way, this derivatives side note,
另外，求该导数
going to be of the log of the likelihood function, the log likelihood.
需要对似然函数求对数，即对数似然
And I'll explain a little bit more why that is,
我讲解释一下为什么是这样
in an advanced section of this module later on, an optional one.
在稍后的高级课程部分，这是选修的
But just think about it as a derivative of the likelihood for now.
对似然函数求导
Now, the derivative of the likelihood is going to be equal to the sum
似然函数的导数等于
over the data points, so we're going to consider that each data point has
数据点的和，我们将考虑每个数据点
a contribution to the derivative, some only want to make the derivative big,
是否对导数有影响，一些会使导数变大
some like to make the derivative smaller, but we're going to sum over the data
一些会使导数变小，但我们要对他们求和
points of the difference between what's called the indicator function that
指示函数表示后的结果是不同的
a data point is plus 1, so indicator of whether this data point is positive.
数据点加1，表明该点是正的
So I'm going to specify it at the bottom here.
所以我要在底部指定它
So let's get our ink.
让我们拿笔标记一下
So this indicated function simply say output 1 if
这个函数表明输出为1
yi is truly a positive example.
如果yi为正样本
And output 0 if yi is a negative example.
如果yi为负样本输出为0
So that's the indicator is.
这就是指示函数的意思
So this is this definition over here.
这就是此处的定义
So is this a positive example?
这是正样本吗？
And the second term, so there's a difference between that and
第二部分，指示函数值和
whatever my model predicts,
无模型的预测结果不同
that how much my model thus far predict, that xi is positive.
模型预测xi为正的概率是多少
In other words, if this is the difference between the truth, is this a positive
换句话说，这与真实值不同
example and the likelihood that my model science to being a positive example.
这是一个正样本，模型的似然也将是一个正例
And we're going to weigh it by the feature value xj.
对特征值xj加权重
So this, for example, is the number of awesomes.
例如，这是awesomes的个数
So if later point has many awesomes,
所以如果之后的点有很多awesomes
then it has more contributions of the the derivative because that coefficient's
将会对导数值产生较大影响
going to be multiplied by say 20 awesomes.
因为系数将扩大20倍
If you have zero awesomes, then there's no contribution here because weather
如果我们有0个awesomes，将不会有任何影响
the coefficient is high or low doesn't make any difference is the data point.
因为无论系数大还是小都不会有什么区别
So that's why we weigh that way.
这就是我们这样加权的原因
So this is exactly the derivative that's very simple that we're going to implement.
这就是我们将要实现的求导
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community